{
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "1 &times; 5",
      "answer": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "-6 &times; -6",
      "answer": "36"
    },
    {
      "question": "-11 &times; 9",
      "answer": "-99"
    },
    {
      "question": "2 &times; 8",
      "answer": "16"
    },
    {
      "question": "-10 &times; 2",
      "answer": "-20"
    },
    {
      "question": "-2 &times; 4",
      "answer": "-8"
    },
    {
      "question": "4 &times; -4",
      "answer": "-16"
    },
    {
      "question": "-12 &times; 12",
      "answer": "-144"
    },
    {
      "question": "10 &times; -4",
      "answer": "-40"
    },
    {
      "question": "-10 &times; 9",
      "answer": "-90"
    },
    {
      "question": "11 &times; -7",
      "answer": "-77"
    },
    {
      "question": "3 &times; 0",
      "answer": "0"
    },
    {
      "question": "4 &times; -7",
      "answer": "-28"
    },
    {
      "question": "5 &times; 5",
      "answer": "25"
    },
    {
      "question": "-1 &times; 11",
      "answer": "-11"
    },
    {
      "question": "-2 &times; 7",
      "answer": "-14"
    },
    {
      "question": "2 &times; -2",
      "answer": "-4"
    },
    {
      "question": "-12 &times; 1",
      "answer": "-12"
    },
    {
      "question": "6 &times; -1",
      "answer": "-6"
    },
    {
      "question": "-2 &times; -9",
      "answer": "18"
    },
    {
      "question": "-12 &times; 6",
      "answer": "-72"
    },
    {
      "question": "5 &times; -10",
      "answer": "-50"
    },
    {
      "question": "2 &times; 10",
      "answer": "20"
    },
    {
      "question": "-7 &times; -8",
      "answer": "56"
    },
    {
      "question": "-2 &times; 9",
      "answer": "-18"
    },
    {
      "question": "-5 &times; -11",
      "answer": "55"
    },
    {
      "question": "-9 &times; -6",
      "answer": "54"
    },
    {
      "question": "12 &times; 5",
      "answer": "60"
    },
    {
      "question": "7 &times; -10",
      "answer": "-70"
    },
    {
      "question": "-12 &times; -10",
      "answer": "120"
    },
    {
      "question": "11 &times; -6",
      "answer": "-66"
    },
    {
      "question": "-9 &times; 8",
      "answer": "-72"
    },
    {
      "question": "2 &times; -9",
      "answer": "-18"
    },
    {
      "question": "3 &times; 7",
      "answer": "21"
    },
    {
      "question": "-6 &times; 2",
      "answer": "-12"
    },
    {
      "question": "5 &times; -1",
      "answer": "-5"
    },
    {
      "question": "-2 &times; -2",
      "answer": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "-9 &times; -9",
      "answer": "81"
    },
    {
      "question": "1 &times; 11",
      "answer": "11"
    },
    {
      "question": "10 &times; -6",
      "answer": "-60"
    },
    {
      "question": "-4 &times; 12",
      "answer": "-48"
    },
    {
      "question": "4 &times; 10",
      "answer": "40"
    },
    {
      "question": "6 &times; 12",
      "answer": "72"
    },
    {
      "question": "6 &times; 10",
      "answer": "60"
    },
    {
      "question": "12 &times; 11",
      "answer": "132"
    },
    {
      "question": "-4 &times; 2",
      "answer": "-8"
    },
    {
      "question": "12 &times; -10",
      "answer": "-120"
    },
    {
      "question": "4 &times; 11",
      "answer": "44"
    },
    {
      "question": "-5 &times; 6",
      "answer": "-30"
    },
    {
      "question": "-10 &times; -2",
      "answer": "20"
    }
  ]
}
